I still can't believe that it's what
and Edward Snowden's being a traitor is
still up for discussion.
I wanted to reach into the TV and smack
half those senators on the Senate
Intelligence Committee across the face.
This insistence on the use of the word
traitor. There is a constitutional
definition of treason. It's providing
aid and comfort to the enemy in a time
of war. He didn't provide aid and
comfort to the enemy and we're not in a
time of war. So, you can choose to not
like what he did.
But he's not a traitor by any legal
definition. In my view, Ed Snowden is a
bonafide American hero. You can disagree
with me if you want, but I think the guy
has done a national service of historic
proportions because without him we would
never have known that the government was
spying on us. When I was in prison, his
dad came to visit me and I gave his dad
a letter that he gave to a mutual friend
of ours who was going to Moscow to see
Ed. And I said, you have to hire the
best lawyers money can buy. Hire my
lawyers, which he did. He hired my
lawyers. He was willing to come home. He
was willing to go to prison. All he
asked of the Justice Department is that
they allow him to stand up in court and
explain why he did what he did and DOJ
said, absolutely not.
How could you possibly object to that?
And another thing, too, that these
idiots on the Senate Intelligence
Committee are so wrong about. Angus
King, the independent Democrat from
Maine said this, that he defected to
Russia. No, he did not defect to Russia.
He was in the transit lounge at Moscow
Airport on his way to Ecuador when John
Kerry revoked his passport. John Kerry
stranded him in Russia. I'm hoping that
Donald Trump has the guts to stand up
and actually pardon him and let him come
home. His His moved out to Moscow and
they got married there and they they
have two sons now. He's just a working
guy, but he he should have the right to
come home.